<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Neat</title>
    <link>/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Neat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the ThemeForest Standard license</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/getting-started/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started/installation/</guid>
      <description>Installation Follow these simple steps to get up and running with Neat.
1. Install NodeJS Download and install NodeJS as Neat uses NodeJS &amp;amp; npm to manage its dependencies.
  node -v   2. Update NPM Node comes with npm installed so you should have a version of npm. However, npm gets updated more frequently than Node does, so you’ll want to make sure it’s the latest version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build System</title>
      <link>/getting-started/build-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started/build-system/</guid>
      <description>Build System Neat uses GulpJS as the main build system, its use of streams and code-over-configuration makes for a simpler and more intuitive build.
Setup To use Gulp, you must have NodeJS installed and NodeJS will have npm (node package manager). To get started follow our instructions from the installation guide.
Once you have succesfully setup, now you can use Neat Gulp CLI commands to automate your tasks.
Commands All GulpJS tasks and configurations, can be found at gulpfile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vendors</title>
      <link>/getting-started/vendors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started/vendors/</guid>
      <description>Vendors Thrid-party librairies / dependencies like Bootstrap Grid, Feather icons and jQuery.
How we manage vendors?  We install vendors using NPM package manager. Using GulpJS (copy-assets task), we copy the required files from node_modules/into our src/ folder. If it&amp;rsquo;s a css file, it will be copied into our src/scss/vendor folder. If it&amp;rsquo;s a javascript/jquery file, it will be copied into our src/js/vendor. Again, using GulpJS we rename these files and optimize them for the build process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>